[
    {
        "question": "Which EC2 service can be used without charge under the Free Tier?",
        "answer": "t2.micro EC2 instance type instances for a total of 750 hours per month"
    },
    {
        "question": "You want to experiment with deploying a web server on an EC2 instance. Which two of the following resources can you include to make that work while remaining within the Free Tier?",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "A 5 GB bucket on S3"
            },
            {
                "option": "A t2.micro instance type EC2 instance"
            },
            {
                "option": "A 30 GB solid-state Elastic Block Store (EBS) drive"
            },
            {
                "option": "Two 20 GB solid-state Elastic Block Store (EBS) drives"
            }
        ],
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "A t2.micro instance type EC2 instance"
            },
            {
                "answer": "A 30 GB solid-state Elastic Block Store (EBS) drive"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following usage will always be cost-free even after your account’s Free Tier has expired?",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "One million API calls/month on Amazon API Gateway"
            },
            {
                "option": "10 GB of data retrievals from Amazon Glacier per month"
            },
            {
                "option": "500 MB/month of free storage on the Amazon Elastic Container Registry (ECR)"
            },
            {
                "option": "10 custom monitoring metrics and 10 alarms on Amazon CloudWatch"
            }
        ],
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "10 GB of data retrievals from Amazon Glacier per month"
            },
            {
                "answer": "A 10 custom monitoring metrics and 10 alarms on Amazon CloudWatch"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which tools are available to ensure you won’t accidentally run past your Free Tier limit and incur unwanted costs?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Automated email alerts when activity approaches the Free Tier limits"
            },
            {
                "answer": "The Top Free Tier Services by Usage section on the Billing & Cost Management Dashboard"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is likely to be an accurate source of AWS pricing information?",
        "answer": "AWS online documentation relating to a particular service"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which will probably not affect the pricing for an AWS service?",
        "answer": "Requests for raising the available service limit"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is a limitation of the AWS Simple Monthly Calculator?",
        "answer": "Not all AWS services are included"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Simple Monthly Calculator selections will likely have an impact on most other configuration choices on the page?",
        "answers": [
            {
                "answer": "Free Usage Tier"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Choose Region"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is not an included parameter in the AWS Total Cost of Ownership Calculator?",
        "answer": "The tax implications of a cloud deployment"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which AWS Total Cost of Ownership Calculator parameters is likely to have the greatest impact on cost?",
        "answer": "Number of servers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following AWS documentation URLs points to the page containing an up-to-date list of service limits?",
        "options": [
            {
                "option": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/limits.html"
            },
            {
                "option": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/aws_service_limits.html"
            },
            {
                "option": "https://aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/aws_service_limits.html"
            },
            {
                "option": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/latest/gr/aws_service_limits.html"
            }
        ],
        "answer": "https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/aws_service_limits.html"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which describes one possible reason for AWS service limits?",
        "answer": "To prevent individual customers from accidentally launching a crippling level of resource consumption"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it always possible to request service limit increases from AWS?",
        "answer": "No. Some service limits are hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the best place to get a quick summary of this month’s spend for your account?",
        "answer": "Billing & Cost Management Dashboard"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main goal for creating a Usage budget type (in AWS Budgets)?",
        "answer": "To track particular categories of resource consumption"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is not a setting you can configure in a Cost budget?",
        "answer": "Owner (username of resource owner)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main difference between the goals of Cost Explorer and of cost and usage reports?",
        "answer": "Cost Explorer displays visualizations of high-level historical and current account costs, while cost and usage reports generate granular usage reports in CSV format"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of cost allocation tags?",
        "answer": "To help you identify resources for the purpose of tracking your account spending"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which scenarios would be a good use case for AWS Organizations?",
        "answer": "A single company with multiple AWS accounts that wants a single place to administrate everything. A company that’s integrated some operations with an upstream vendor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these tools lets you design graphs within the browser interface to track your account spending?",
        "answer": "Budgets"
    }
]    